Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937-2012 UA.27.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accessions UA88-57, UA91-53, UA2008-0048, UA2008-0065, UA2012-0041, 6
  - MLK part 3 created 12/10/07, 2007-12-10; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0029)
  - Sarah P. Duke Gardens, undated; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0030)
  - Duke University Graduate School Where Your Presence Matters, 2005; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0031)
  - Med Minute Audio, 2004-2005; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0032)
  - David Horowitz at Duke 3/7/06, 2006-03-07; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0033)
  - The Professor and the Pep Band (Steve Nowicki) 5 min. ESPN 3/10/06, 2006-03-10; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0034)
  - Grant Hill Art Collection CBS Sunday Morning (10 min) 4/2/06, 2006-04-02; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0035)
  - Dean William Schlesinger NSOE UNC-TV 12/12/06, 2006-12-12; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0036)
  - Duke's Teacher Grants 3 Clips 2/22/06, 2006-02-22; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0037)
  - Tavis Smiley Show-PBS John Hope Franklin 2/14/06, 2006-02-14; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0038)
  - Ebrahim Moosa "Ethical Challenges in Contemporary Islamic Thought" 10/9/07 Fez, Morocco, 2007-10-09; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0039)
  - HBO "Costas Now" inc. Coach K profile 1 hr. 3/07, 2007 March; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0040)
  - President Brodhead Poetry Reading 1/31/06, 2006-01-31; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0041)
  - Jeopardy! (lemurs) 2/28/06, 2006-02-28; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0042)
  - Undergraduate Convocation address RH Brodhead (copy) 8/22/07 11am, 2007-08-22; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0043)
  - NC Now Duke Libraries Newspaper Repository 2/23/06 7 min., 2006-02-23; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0044)
  - Madeline Morris Foreign Relations Testimony 7/21/06, 2006-07-21; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0045)
  - A Cut Above: 100 Seasons of Duke Basketball, 2005; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0046)
  - Duke Gardens: "Crown Jewel of Duke University", 2004; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0047)
  - A Video Tribute to John Burness, 2008-05-13; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0048)
  - A Video Tribute to John Burness, 2008-05-13; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0049)
  - "A Conversation in One Brief Afternoon" with Richard Brodhead, Nannerl Keohane, and Judy Woodruff, 2004-02-01; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0050)
  - Ambitions Realized: A Nod to Nan, 2003-10-03; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0051)
  - "A Salute to Jerry Black," Facilities Management Department, 2003 September; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0052)
  - Opening Convocation 2006, Duke Chapel, 2006-08-23; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0053)
  - French Family Sceince Center, Dedication Ceremony, November 9, 2007, 2007-09-09; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0054)
  - Brodhead Griffith Theatre, Part 2, undated; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0055)
  - Brodhead Griffith Theatre, Part 2, undated; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0056)
  - Brodhead Clip 2, undated; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0057)
  - President Brodhead at City Club of Cleveland, 2006-11-10; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0058)
  - MLK 2003 Lani Guinier Keynote 1/19/03, 2003-01-19; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0001)
  - MLK Angela Davis 1/17/05, 2005-01-17; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0002)
  - Commencement, 1998, George H. W. Bush, audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0003)
  - Tom Wolfe, 2002-05-12; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0004)
  - John Hope Franklin Progs. Conf., undated; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0005)
  - Duke University Commencement speech by David Gergen, 1995; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0006)
  - Duke Newsline, Inauguration, 1993-10-28; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0007)
  - Inauguration 1993, 1993-10-23; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0008)
  - Janet Reno speech, 1994-01-22; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0009)
  - Convocation, Nan Keohane, 1995-08-24; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0010)
  - 100 Years of Duke in Durham, undated; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0011)
  - Bill King, 100 Years of Duke in Durham, undated; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0012)
  - Founder's Day 1993, 1993-12-09; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0013)
  - Founders' Day Convocation, Locke, 1998, 10/1/1998; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0014)
  - Dan Mallory, Speaker, 2001, audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0015)
  - Endowment Announcement, undated; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0016)
  - Janet Reno speech, 1993-05-16; audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0017)
  - Graduation 1999, Sam Wood speech, Cokie Roberts speech, audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0018)
  - Graduation 1999, Cokie Roberts speech, audiocassette (Box 30, Audio-cassette UA27.02.0001-CS-0019)
  - "Some Reflections on Racial Inequality in the United States" by Dr. John Hope Franklin Nelson Music Room, 2005-01-20; Dvcam (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-Dvcam-0001)
  - Lafferty, NOK, 1995-03-29; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0047)
  - Professor Alex Roland/Glenn Space Flight, Lehrer News Hour (PBS), 1998-10-28; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0155)
  - 1996 Highlights, Tape 1, VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0156)
  - Professor Bruce Jentleson, "Mideast Turmoil," Fox News, 2002-04-10; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0157)
  - Susan Tifft, 2003-05-23; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0158)
  - PBS Newshour, Russia TV Crackdown and "The Quilts of Gee's Bend", 2003-07-01; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0159)
  - Duke News Service, News Clip Archive, 2002-01-18/2002-04-02; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0160)
  - Shroud of Turin, CBS Evening News, Danin; Fire Turin Cathedral, 1997-04-11; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0161)
  - Good Morning America, Dr. John Simon, UV-A Ray Protection/Photoaging), 1998-09-02; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0162)
  - "Bright Minds," Duke University, Talent Identification, 1992; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0163)
  - 48 Hours, WRAL-TV/CBS Network, 1988-02-16; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0165)
  - Video College Guide Segment, undated; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0166)
  - North Carolina People #1536 -- William Friday (host) and Keith Brodie (guest), undated; VHS (Box 31, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0168)
  - Karen Paschall Memorial Duke Chapel, 1994 April; mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0001)
  - Rosalynn Carter Institute for Care at End of Life 3/2/00, 2000-03-02; mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0002)
  - President Brodhead WUNC-FM SOT 10/18/05, 2005-10-18; mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0003)
  - John Hope Franklin, 09-17; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0004)
  - Dr. Snyderman, 2001-02-13; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0005)
  - Sally: Ms. Meachum, 2007-02-12; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0006)
  - Duke News, undated; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0007)
  - Snyderman (TSOT), WUNC-FM, 2002-02-05; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0008)
  - Andy Bey "phoner" and Susan Reeve, 2007-08-29; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0009)
  - Brodhead Inauguration, Faculty Panel, "Duke Past, present and Future", 2004-09-18; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0010)
  - Brodhead Inauguration, Faculty Panel, "Global Health," Disc 1, 2004-09-18; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0011)
  - Brodhead Inauguration, Faculty Panel, "Global Health," Disc 2, 2004-09-18; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0012)
  - LAX Report (phone) press copy, 2006-05-08; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0013)
  - Graduation 2002, 2002-05-12; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0014)
  - Women's Initiative, press copy, 2003-09-23; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0015)
  - President Brodhead with students, 2005-03-22; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0016)
  - Duke University Commencement 2006 address by John Hope Franklin, 2006-05-14; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0017)
  - Academic Freedom panel, 2004-03-01; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0018)
  - Tom Wolfe, Festival of the Book, 2006-04-29; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0019)
  - Elizabeth Dole 2000 Commencement, 2000-05-14; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0020)
  - President Briodhead Graduation, 2004, 2004-05-09; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0021)
  - Duke Convocation 2006, 2006-08-23; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0022)
  - Commencement Speeches 2003, 2003-05-11; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0023)
  - Graduation 2001, 2001-05-13; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0024)
  - President News Conference, President Brodhead, Announcement of Selection, 2003-12-12; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0025)
  - Brodhead Inauguration, Faculty Panel, "Global Challenges", 2004-09-18; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0026)
  - President Brodhead media event, 2004-06-30; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0027)
  - President Brodhead Inauguration, Faculty Panel, "Global Culture.", 2004-09-17; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0028)
  - Duke Convocation 2000, 2000-08-24; Mini-disc (Box 32, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-MDV-0029)
  - Digital Audio, 1998-2010; 1709 files including mostly digital audio files; approximately 17 gigabytes.
    Electronic records in this file have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
  - Digital Video, 2000-2010; 4903 files including mostly digital image, video, and audio files; approximately 354 gigabytes.
  - Digital Images, 2006-2008; 104 digital image files; approximately 805 megabytes.
  - Multimedia, 1999-2012; 2951 files including mostly digital image and HTML files; approximately 853 megabytes.